New York, NY

kenny.johnson.nyc@gmail.com

Kennyj.dev

213-446-7268

LinkedIn.com/in/kenny-johnson-nyc/

Github/papercircuit

Creative and dedicated professional with a unique background in music and experience in a marketing/consulting startup. A recent graduate of Fullstack Academy's immersive web development bootcamp, Kenny is passionate about collaboration and embraces challenges in software development, testing, and bug fixing.

SKILLS

Languages/Libraries: React, Javascript, Shopify/Liquid, Express, Axios, Node.js, Tailwind CSS, Highcharts, Git, VSCode

Design: Figma, Sketch, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER / CLUB MED

AUG 2022 - CURRENT

- Worked closely with the design team at Club Med to bring mockups to life using Dartangan CMS
- Utilized Figma, Miro, and Adobe InDesign to interpret designs and understand project requirements
- Built pixel-perfect marketing emails using the proprietary builder Dartagnan
- Ensured all emails met design and branding standards through attention to detail and quality assurance practices

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER / TANGOSQUARED

OCT 2022 - FEB 2023

- · Managed and provided technical support for fashion brand Suzie Kondi
- Resolved technical issues through help tickets and direct communication with the client
- Built a range of pages for the client's Shopify site using Liquid
- · Contributed to the redesign of a WordPress client's site
- · Utilized JavaScript, Liquid, and CSS to implement design and functionality improvements

PROJECTS

SATELLITE LOCATION VISUALIZER

 Developed a 3D satellite visualizer leveraging Highcharts, Axios, and Vanilla JavaScript, integrating NASA's Space Physics Data Facility API for accurate satellite data representation.

STOCK MARKET TRADING SIMULATOR

• Collaborated on a two-person team to create a stock market trading simulator using AWS and React, simulating real-world stock data for risk-free trading practice with virtual currency.

EDUCATION

FULLSTACK ACADEMY | BOOTCAMP

Web Development Immersive / New York, NY 2022-2023

MUSICIAN'S INSTITUTE | BACHELORS Music Composition / Hollywood, CA 2008-2010